# STACIE D. SUMMERS

1022 Briarcrest Lane ♦ Cookeville, TN 38501 ♦ (618) 201-4724 ♦ sdsummers 921@gmail.com

A skilled and effective customer service professional with over 15 years of customer service experience in the retail, healthcare, and hospitality space. Recent graduate of Computer Programming 2-year program looking for the opportunity to bridge computer science degree with customer service experience. Proven track record leading and developing highly engage teams. A passionate and action-orientated service professional who takes complete ownership of the customer service experience.

#### SKILLS & COMPETENCIES

Leadership, Training & Team Development
Client Relationship Management
Project Management
Strategic Planning
Visual Studio
HTML5 and CSS

Process Development & Implementation
Hardware/Software Certification
Object Oriented Programming
Full Stack Web Development
Customer Service
Python
C#

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## WILDWOOD RESORT & MARINA — Granville, TN

#### Concierge Manager, 2021- Current

- Drove change initiatives to increase customer satisfaction by creating quality standards including scripting for telecommunications and in-person guest relations.
- ◆ Creation and implementation of resort-wide annual review system to evaluate and elevate employee performance. Responsible for Annual Employee Reviews and Evaluations for Concierge Representatives.
- Development of a standardized training program to ensure consistent guest experience and reduction of reservation errors.
- Implemented multiple process changes to increase guest and customer satisfaction by reducing cross departmental friction points which negatively affected guest experiences and outcomes.
- Successful implementation and coordination of a cross training program to increase productivity and reduction of staffing deficiencies across multiple departments, resulting in reduced labor costs during winter season.
- Instituted a new promotional structure program based on service promotion to increase productivity and employee engagement.
- Instilled best practices for computer use by employees throughout resort to enhance cyber security.

## WABASH GENERAL HOSPITAL — Mount Carmel, IL

#### Orthopedic Scribe, 2019 - Current

- Top performing scribe for WGH Orthopedic department, specializing in appointments for evaluation of the spine and osteoporosis screenings/treatments, and utilized as training resource with new hires.
- Effectively reduced denied claims and maximized reimbursements by educating staff on proper code usage and pre-authorization practices.

- Creation and implementation of training documentation, scribe templates, and best practices for specialized appointments for Better Bones osteoporosis clinic.
- Played integral role in reducing patient appointment wait times while upholding excellent patient satisfaction and outcomes.

#### COOKEVILLE REGIONAL MEIDCAL CENTER — Cookeville, TN

## Patient Registration Representative II, 2018 - 2019

- Recognized as top-level representative promoted from level I to level II within first six months of hire date.
- ♦ Holds record-setting collection for ER copays in 1 month totaling \$10,000, exceeding previous record by approximately \$4,000 and collaborated with team to consistently ensure completion of Registration Department collection goals.
- Responsible for managing patient information and insurance verification quickly and efficiently for ER and after-hours hospital admissions to reduce delays in patient testing, treatment, and transfers.
- Monitored patient tracking applications and work closely with multiple departments to prioritize registration of patients based on triage status and improved patient care.
- CHAA certification completed.

#### **HEALTH FIRST** — Viera, FL

# Patient Services Specialist II, 2017 - 2018

- Identified as top performer in quality and utilized as training resource with newly onboarded team members.
- Fundamental in deployment of in-person scheduling program at satellite facilities, increasing customer access to care and collaborating across multiple departments to improve the consumer journey.
- Utilized Yellow Belt Six Sigma training to reduce time spent on calls for MRI scheduling and shorten time span for scheduling available MRI appointments.
- Monitored call queues and worked as a cohesive member of the call center scheduling team to reduce call wait times for patients scheduling diagnostic tests.
- Educated patients on proper procedures, protocols and testing preparations for advanced diagnostic testing to ensure best possible outcomes of patient testing.
- Actively contributed and participated in weekly staff meetings to devise ways to meet department goals and improve performance.

#### LEE N SHELDON, DMD — Melbourne, FL

#### Treatment Coordinator, 2014 - 2017

- Managed schedules and inbound inquiries for new patients to increase number of weekly new patient appointments by 25% while simultaneously increasing appointment for patient treatment.
- Coordinated monthly educational presentations to potential patients.
- Performed and tracked diagnostic testing to aid in periodontal evaluation of patient. Developed effective and affordable treatment plans based on results of evaluation to assist patients in receiving necessary and desired treatments.
- Responsible for the training of staff to properly and efficiently complete front desk job requirements.
- Acted as patient liaison for claims submitted to insurance companies to maximize reimbursement to patients.

# **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS**

# VOLUNTEER STATE COMMUNITY COLLEGE — Cookeville, TN

Graduated 2021

- ◆ Computer Programming AAS
- Project Manager
- Secretary of VSCC Cyber Security Club 2019 2020

## LEAN SIX SIMGA YELLOW BELT CERTIFIED

2016 - Health First.

• Project member tasked with data collection process to assist in the reduction of average wait time for scheduled MRIs across Health First health systems.

## PC PRO HARDWARE/SOFTWARE CERTIFICATION— Cookeville, TN

2020

◆ Completed PC Pro A+ Hardware/Software Certification

# CERFITIED HEALTHCARE ACCESS ASSOCIATE - Cookeville, TN

2020

• Completed CHAA Certification as part of continuing education at CRMC.